Guide to the Time Inc. Sports Illustrated Publishing and Business Records 1950s-1993 MS 3009-RG 35
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Advertising Promotion Department Records, 1950s-1987; 28.1 Linear feet in 29 record cartons, 1 document case, and 1 flat box
  - Subseries VI.A. Special Events and Publicity Director Keith Morris Files, 1957-1980; 20.6 Linear feet in 20 record cartons, 1 document case, and 1 flat box
    - Subsubseries VI.A.2. Awards Files, 1957-1981; 1.75 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
      - Sportsman/Sportswoman of the Year: 1972: Billie Jean King and John Wooden (Offsite-box 4121, Folder 19-21)
        1 film reel; 16mm. On label: "1972 Sportsman and Woman of the Year."
      - Sportsman/Sportswoman of the Year: 1977: Steve Cauthen (Offsite-box 4121, Folder 22)
      - Sportsman/Sportswoman of the Year: 1978: Jack Nicklaus (Offsite-box 4121, Folder 23)
      - Sportsman/Sportswoman of the Year: 1979: Terry Bradshaw and Willie Stargell (Offsite-box 4121, Folder 24)
      - Sportsman/Sportswoman of the Year: 1981: Sugar Ray Leonard (Offsite-box 4122, Folder 1)
    - Subsubseries VI.A.3. Promotional Events Photographs, 1954-1959; 2 Linear feet in 2 record cartons and 1 flat box
      Promotional Events Photographs contains primarily photographic material of events planned or sponsored by Sports Illustrated (SI). There is a small amount of papers although many folders contain only photographs or negatives. Of note are the records about the SI launch party.
      Organized chronologically then alphabetically based on the original loosely chronological arrangement.
      - Pre-publication Publicity, circa 1954 (Offsite-box 4122, Folder 2-3)
      - Sports Illustrated Launch Party, 1954 (Offsite-box 4122, Folder 4)
      - First Anniversary Sullivan Show, 1955 August (Offsite-box 4122, Folder 5)
      - [Sullivan Show?] Davis Clip Photographs, 1955 (Offsite-box 4122, Folder 6)
      - Olympic Team Members, 1956 (Offsite-box 4122, Folder 7)
      - Sports Day: Ridgewood, NJ, 1956 (Offsite-box 4122, Folder 8-9)
      - [Sports Day?]: Ruth Lieder, 1956 (Offsite-box 4122, Folder 10)
      - Sullivan Show, 1956 (Offsite-box 4122, Folder 11)
      - Floyd Patterson on the Tex and Jinx, 1957 (Offsite-box 4122, Folder 12)
      - Goren Playing Bridge with Dodgers, 1957 (Offsite-box 4122, Folder 13)
      - Jaycees in New York and at West Point, 1957 (Offsite-box 4122, Folder 14)
      - John Norwood on Tonight Show, 1957 (Offsite-box 4147, Folder 2)
      - Summer Sports Festival: Cross Country / Gimbels (Cheltenham, NY) / Northland Center (Detroit, MI) / Old Orchard, 1957 (Offsite-box 4122, Folder 15-21)
      - West Islip High school Swimming Pool Opening / Aquacade, 1957 November (Offsite-box 4123, Folder 1-2)
      - Alex Olmedo Press Lunch, circa 1958 (Offsite-box 4123, Folder 3)
      - Baseball Series, 1958 (Offsite-box 4123, Folder 4)
      - Jaycee-Sports Illustrated Youth Fitness, 1958 (Offsite-box 4123, Folder 5)
      - Jordan Marsh Sports Festival, 1958 February (Offsite-box 4123, Folder 6-7)
      - Koehler High School Trampoline Tour, 1958 (Offsite-box 4123, Folder 8)
      - People to People Sports Committee Dinner, 1958 September (Offsite-box 4123, Folder 9)
      - Polk Brothers Shows: Chicago, 1958 (Offsite-box 4123, Folder 10)
      - Rockefeller Center Festival, 1958 July (Offsite-box 4123, Folder 11-16)
      - Southdale Shopping Center Promotion, 1958 June (Offsite-box 4123, Folder 17)
      - Sports Car Driver of 1957 Press Reception, 1958 (Offsite-box 4123, Folder 18)
      - Sportsman of the Year 1957 Presentation, 1958 (Offsite-box 4123, Folder 19)
      - Sportsman of the Year 1957: Ed Sullivan Show, 1958 January (Offsite-box 4123, Folder 20)
      - Sportsman of the Year: Lunch, 1958? (Offsite-box 4123, Folder 21)
      - Sports Illustrated Broadway Sign Opening Ceremonies, 1959? (Offsite-box 4123, Folder 22)
    - Subsubseries VI.A.4. Recordings of Sports Figures Interviews [RESTRICTED], 1960s-1986; 3.25 Linear feet in 4 record cartons containing 142 items and 2 folders
      This series contains recordings of several hundred interviews conducted by Keith Morris of sports figures, possibly as part of the Sports Illustrated tape service, to be sent out to media stations. Some interviews are of athletes named Sportsman or Sportswoman of the Year, winners of top honors in their sport, and Olympic competitors. Besides current and former athletes, subjects include coaches, managers, and sportscasters. The majority of interviews date from 1980 to 1986. Each tape could contain up to five different interviews.
      Organized by interviews definitely conducted by Morris then by interviews probably conducted by Morris. Items in each category are organized as chronologically as possible.
      - Interviews, 1960s (Offsite-box 4124, Item 1-2)
        2 audiotape reels: analog; 4 in., 1/4 in. tape.
        illegible names
        Brooks Robinson/Baltimore Orioles
        Tony Conigliaro/Boston Red Sox
      - Interviews, 1977 (Offsite-box 4126, Folder 1)
        1 film reel; 16mm
        Sam Snead
      - Interviews, 1980, 1982 (Offsite-box 4125, Item 21-23)
        3 film reels; 16mm.
        Muhammed Ali
        Sugar Ray Leonard
      - Interviews, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 4126, Item 1)
        1 film reel; 16mm.
        Mike Eruzione/Sportsman of the Year 1980
        Sugar Ray Leonard/Sportsman of the Year 1981
      - Interviews, 1983 January 11-March 29 (Offsite-box 4124, Item 3-12)
        10 audiotape reels: analog; 4 in., 1/4 in. tape.
        Bob McAdoo/Los Angeles Lakers
        Maurice Lucas/Phoenix Suns
        John Thompson/Georgetown University basketball coach
        Kevin Laughery/Atlanta Hawks coach
        Bernard King/New York Knicks
        Kareem Abdul Jabbar/Los Angeles Lakers
        Reggie Theus/Chicago Bulls
        Harmon Killebrew/former Minnesota Twins
        Johan Kriek/South African tennis pro
        Johnny Mize/1981 Hall of Famer
        Larry Holmes/Heavyweight Champion of the World
        Billy Martin/New York Yankees former manager
        Pee Wee Reese/Brooklyn Dodgers former player
        Tom Young/Rutgers University basketball coach
        Purvis Short/Golden State Warriors
        Jimmy Connors/world tennis pro
        Dana Kirk/Memphis State basketball coach
        John Hannah/New England Patriots
        Dennis Johnson/Phoenix Suns
        Lee MacPhail/American League baseball president
        Dwight Stones/United States high jump champion
        Joe Torre/Atlanta Braves former manager
        Walt Frazier/New York Knicks former player
        Bill Terry/Hall of Fame baseball star
        Jose-Luis Clerc/Argentina tennis pro
        Dan Quisenberry/Kansas City Royals
        Dale Murphy/Atlanta Braves
        Willie McCovey/San Francisco Giants former player
        Yannick Noah/French tennis champion
        Charlie Gehringer/1949 Hall of Famer
        Lenny Wilkens/Seatlle Super Sonics coach
        Bart Conner/United States Olympic gymnast
        Billy Cunningham/Philadelphia 76ers coach
        Bobby Duhon/New York Giants former player
        Colonel Don Miller/United States Olympic Committee Executive Director
        Ray Fontenot/New York Yankees
        Barry Bonnell/Toronto Blue Jays
        Jesse Orosco/New York Mets
        Charlie Lea/Montreal Expos
        Bill Buckner/Chicago Cubs
        Birtt Burns/Chicago White Sox
        Bobby Murcer/New York Yankees former player
        Rod Carew/California Angels
        Ryne Sandberg/Chicago Cubs
        John McNamara/California Angels manager
        Lonnie Smith/St. Louis Cardinals
        Ron Kittle/Chicago White Sox
        Tom Seaver/New York Mets
        Ralph Houk/Boston Red Sox
        Jason Thompson/Pittsburgh Pirates
      - Interviews, 1983 April 5-July5 (Offsite-box 4124, Item 13-24)
        12 audiotape reels: analog; 4 in., 1/4 in. tape.
        Tom LaSorda/Los Angeles Dodgers manager
        Alan Trammel/Detroit Tigers
        Dick Howser/Kansas City Royals
        Tommy Helms/Cincinnati Reds
        Mark Fidrych/Boston Red Sox Farm Clubs
        Tug McGraw/Philadelphia Phillies
        Bill Laimbeer/Detroit Pistons
        Stan Albeck/San Antonio Spurs coach
        Anthony Carter/Michigan Panthers
        Herschel Walker/New Jersey Generals
        Lance Parrish/Detroit Tigers
        Roy White/New York Yankees coach
        Eamon Coghlan/world record miler
        John Stuper/St. Louis Cardinals
        Billy Taylor/Washington Federals
        Joe Morgan/Philadelphia Phillies
        Chet Lemon/Detroit Tigers
        Dan Mattingly/New York Yankees
        Joe Walton/New York Jets Head Coach
        Red Schoendienst/St. Louis Cardinals coach
        Rick Cerone/New York Yankees
        Billy Gardner/Minnesota Twins manager
        Jesse Barfield/Toronto Blue Jays
        Joe Fields/New York Jets
        Chuck Tanner/Pittsburgh Pirates manager
        Darryl Strawberry/New York Mets
        Joe Niekro/Houston Astros
        Mark Brammer/Buffalo Bills wide receiver
        Ron Oester/Cincinnati Reds
        Mike Torrez/New York Mets
        Dave Righetti/New York Yankees
        Dave Phillips/American League umpire
        Mickey Rivers/Texas Rangers
        Charlie Hough/Texas Rangers
        Steve Garvey/San Diego Padres
        Dickie Thon/Houston Astros
        Murle Breer/golf pro
        Greg Luzinski/Chicago White Sox
        Dave Sax/Los Angeles Dodgers
        Gary Player/golf pro
        Mike Norris/Oakland Athletics
        Kurt Bevacqua/San Diego Padres
        Jimmy Reese/California Angels coach
        Gary Carter/Montreal Expos
        Bob Hope/celebrity sport
        Bill Caudill/Seattle Mariners
        Bob Boone/California Angels
        Bob Knepper/Houston Astros
        Dan Driessen/Cincinnati Reds
        Hale Irwin/golf pro
        Robin Yount/Milwaukee Brewers
        Ozzie Smith/St. Louis Cardinals
        Gary Matthews/Philadelphia Phillies
        Von Hayes/Philadelphia Phillies
        Jack Clark/San Francisco Giants
        Steve Boros/Oakland Athletics manager
        Scott Brunner/New York Giants (football) Quarterback
        Chi-Chi Rodriguez/golf pro
        Jody Davis/Chicago Cubs
      - Interviews, 1983 July 18-November 8 (Offsite-box 4124, Item 25-36)
        Doug Rader/Texas Rangers manager
        Tom Niedenfuer/Los Angeles Dodgers
        Calvin Hill/Cleavland Browns consultant
        Bob Gilder/golf pro
        Dave Wottle/1972 Olympic track champion
        A.J. Duhe/Miami Dolphins linebacker
        Dave Butz/Washington Redskins
        Andrew Dawson/Montreal Expos
        Ron Cey/ Chicago Cubs
        Gene Fullmer/former boxing champion
        Woody Hayes/Former Ohio State University coach
        Mike Hargrove/Cleveland Indians
        Barry Foote/New York Yankees scout
        Keith Fergus/golf pro
        Mark Roth/champion bowler
        Moose Haas/Milkwaukee Brewers
        Manny Trillo/Cleveland Indians
        R.H. Sikes/golf pro
        Mike Heath/Oakland Athletics
        Tom Herr/St. Louis Cardinals
        Doug Flynn/Montreal expos
        Keith Hernandez/New York Mets
        AL Kaline/Detroit Tigers Hall of Famer
        Craig Nettles/New York Yankees
        Lou Whittaker/Detroit Tigers
        Tom Lasorda/Los Angeles Dodgers manager
        Del Crandell/Seattle Mariners manager
        Ted Tollner/University of Southern California football coach
        Jack Youngblood/Los Angeles Rams defensive end
        Brian Kelley/New York Giants linebacker
        Pete Rose/Philadelphia Phillies
        Jim Palmer/Baltimore Orioles
        Harold Jackson/Seattle Seahawks wide receiver
        Jerome Barkum/New York Jets wide receiver
        Lynn Dickey/Green Bay Packers quarterback
        Row Darling/New York Mets
        Gorman Thomas/Cleveland Indians
        Dan Ford/Baltimore Orioles
        Leon Durham/Chicago Cubs
        Rich Gossage/New York Yankees
        Carl Yastrzemski/Boston Red Sox
        Larry O'Brien/NBA commissioner
        Kellen Winslow/San Diego Chargers tight end
        Charlie Moore/Milwaukee Brewers
        Herlin Olsen/Los Angeles Rams Hall of Famer
        Jacob Green/Seattle Seahawks defensive end
        Charlie Joiner/Sand Diego Chargers wide receiver
        Bruce Kison/California Angels
        Gary Hancock/Oakland Athletics
        Lyle Blackwood/Miami Dolphins safety
        Rob Brudzinski/Miami Dolphins linebacker
        Bruce Harper/New York Jets running back
        Don Maloney/New York Rangers
        Jim Mudcat/former baseball pitcher
        Barry Krauss/Baltimore Colts linebacker
        Johnny Lynn/New York Jets defensive back
        Jeff van Note/Atlanta Falcons center
        Scott Hamilton/United States Olympic skater
        Chuck Bednarik/College and Pro Football Hall of Famer
      - Interviews, 1983 November 15-1984 April 10 (Offsite-box 4124, Item 37-49)
        Joe Washington/Washington Redskins running back
        Mike Pagel/Baltimore Colts quarterback
        Doug Cosbie/Dallas Cowboys tight end
        Rob Lanier/Milkwaukee Bucks
        Bill Walton/San Diego Clippers
        Sonny Jurgensen/Hall of Fame quarterback
        Dave Marr/golf pro
        Anthony Dickerson/Dallas Cowboys linebacker
        Len Elmore/New York Knicks
        Elaine Zayak/United States Olympic skater
        Mel Blount/Pittsburgh Steelers defensive back
        Franco Harris/Pittsburgh Steelers running back
        Jim Zorn/Seattle Seahawks quarterback
        Jim Hart/St. Louis Cardinals quarterback
        Ray Malavasi/Los Angeles Rams former head coach
        Kent Benson/Detroit Pistons
        Ralph Sampson/Houston Rockets
        Norm Snead/former NFL quarterback
        Bobby Mitchell/Washington Redskins Hall of Famer
        Floyd Little/Denver Broncos former player
        "Magic" Johnson/Los Angeles Lakers
        Nate Archibald/Milwaukee Bucks
        Bobby Riggs/tennis pro
        Billy Casper/gold pro
        Jose Higueras/Spanish tennis pro
        Bob Beamon/1968 Olympic long jump champion
        Eliot Teltscher/United States tennis pro
        Dick Williams/San Diego Padres manager
        Buck Buchanan/former Kansas City Chiefs star
        Foots Walker/New Jersey Nets
        Neal Broten/Minneapolis North Stars
        Rick Kehoe/Pittsburgh Penguins
        Duanne Sutter/New York Islanders
        Barry Beck/New York Rangers
        Lou Vairo/1984 United States hockey team coach
        Sugar Ray Leonard/former welterweight champion
        Johnny Bench/former Cincinnati Reds star
        Robert Parrish/Boston Celtics
        Ben Davidson/Oakland Raiders former player
        Harrison Dillard/1948-1952 Olympic champion
        Ron Guidry/New York Yankees
        Sleepy Floyd/Golden State Warriors
        Jamaal Wilkes/Los Angeles Lakers
        Jimmy Arias/United States tennis pro
        Darrell Walker/New York Knicks
        Clark Kellogg/Indiana Pacers
        Tony Larussa/Chicago White Sox
        Andres Gomez/Ecuadorian tennis pro
        Bobby Jones/Philadelphia 76ers
        Jim Paxson/Portland Trail Blazers
        John Bach/Golden State Warriors coach
        Angelo Dundee/world famous boxing trainer
        Marv Throneberry/former baseball star
        Don Budge/Hall of Fame tennis pro
        Whitney Herzog/St. Louis Cardinals
        Kent Hrbeck/Minnesota Twins
        Al Holland/Philadelphia Phillies
        Butch Wynegar/New York Yankees
        Tippy Martinez/Baltimore Orioles
        Tom Fears/NFL Hall of Famer
        Garry Shirk/Memphis Show Boats tight end
        Larry Nance/Phoenix Suns
        George Johnson/Indiana Packers
        Don Bragg/1960 Olympic pole vault champion
      - Interviews, 1984 (Offsite-box 4126, Item 2)
        1 videocassette (U-matic) (30 min.); On tape's label: "Designing a New Balance, Bordens Inc., Salary, 10/30/94". On case's label; "Rebecca West 12/14, Keith, Here is a copy of the Tim Daggett/Borden tape for SI -Rebecca".
      - Interviews, 1984 April 17-July 3 (Offsite-box 4124, Item 50-61)
        Mike Smithson/Minnesota Twins
        Sammy Ellis/New York Yankees pitching coach
        Scott Hamilton/1984 Olympic skating champion
        Rich Dotson/Chicago White Sox
        Dave Corzine/Chicago Bulls
        Brent Smith/Montreal Expos
        Bobby Valentine/New York Mets coach
        Charles Hough/Texas Rangers
        Harold Baines/Chicago White Sox
        Dick Schofield/former baseball star
        Phil Niekro/New York Yankees
        Jerry Koosman/Philadelphia Phillies
        Bill Virdoin/Montreal Expos manager
        Mickey Hatcher/Minnesota Twins
        Don Sutton/Milwaukee Brewers
        Buddy Bell/Texas Rangers
        Vern Ruhle/Houston Astros
        Buddy Hackett/celebrity sport
        Cedric Maxwell/Boston Celtics
        Gary Matthews/Chicago Cubs
        Tony Perez/Cincinnati Reds
        Pat Tabler/Cleveland Indians
        Cookie Rojas/California Angels scout
        Dom Baylor/New York Yankees
        Tommy John/California Angels
        Ozzie Virgil/Philadelphia Phillies
        Terry Puhl/Houston Astros
        George Frazier/Cleveland Indians
        Brad Gulden/Cincinnati Reds
        Alvin Davis/Seattle Mariners
        Bruce Benedict/Atlanta Braves
        Darrell Porter/St. Louis Cardinals
        Mel Stottlemyre Jr./1984 Olympic baseball
        Dwight Evans/Boston Red Sox
        Joe Morgan/Oakland Athletics
        Rex Caldwell/golf pro
        Wayne Gretsky/Edmonton Oilers
        Roger Maris/former New York Yankees star
        Robert Goulet/celebrity sport
        Sparky Anderson/Detroit Tigers manager
        Bob Brenly/San Francisco Giants
        "Goose" Gossage/San Diego Padres
        Mike Marshall/Los Angeles Dodgers
        Phil Regan/Seattle Mariners coach
        Marvin Hagler/middleweight champion
        Billy Mills/1964 Olympic track champion
        John Lowenstein/Baltimore Orioles
        Bill Russell/Los Angeles Dodgers
        Peter Jacobsen/golf pro
        Toni Tenille/celebrity sport
        Pete Rose/Montreal Expos
        Hubie Brooks/New York Mets
        Steve Kemp/New York Yankees
        Ray Meyer/DePaul University basketball former coach
        Bill Rogers/golf pro
        Jamie Farr/celebrity sport
        Jack Morris/Detroit Tigers
        Gery Carter/Montreal Expos
        Oscar Robertson/1960 Olympic pole vault champion
        Gary Pettis/California Angels
        Paul Anka/celebrity sport
      - Interviews, 1984 July 9-October 9 (Offsite-box 4124, Item 62-74)
        Floyd Patterson/1984 Olympic boxing preview
        Al Oerter/Olympic gold medal discus champion
        Ken Oberfell/Atlanta Braves
        Roger Clemens/Boston Red Sox
        Dave Parker/Cincinnati Reds
        George Brett/Kansas City Royals
        Dan Marino/Miami Dolphins quarterback
        Randy White/Dallas Cowboys defensive tackle
        Amos Otis/Pittsburgh Pirates
        Ray Knight/Houston Astros
        Mike Buddicker/Balitmore Orioles
        Kevin Keegan/world class English soccer star
        Tony Oliva/former Minnesota Twins star
        Kent Tekulve/Pittsburgh Pirates
        Alvin Dark/former baseball player and manager
        "Moose" Skowrow/former New York Yankees star
        Tony Trabert/Hall of Fame tennis pro
        Bobby Richardson/New York Yankees former player
        Frank Tanana/Texas Rangers
        Tito Landrum/St. Louis Cardinals
        Andre Thornton/Cleveland Indians
        Jim Simons/golf pro
        Gary Lucas/Montreal Expos
        Ali Haji-Sheikh/New York Giants kicker
        Moose Haas/Milwaukee Brewers
        Sam McDowell/former Pirates pitcher
        Glen Wilson/Philadelphia Phillies
        Dave Engle/Minnesota Twins
        Pat Sheridan/Kansas City Royals
        Alan Ashby/Houston Astros
        Floyd Bannister/Chicago White Sox
        Bruce Sutter/St. Louis Cardinals
        Jim Lonborg/Red Sox former pitcher
        Tom Tresh/New York Yankees former star
        Bert Blyleven/Cleveland Indians
        Dave Winfield/New York Yankees
        Stan Walters/Philadelphia Eagles former player
        Jerry Robinson/Philadelphia Eagles linebacker
        Phil McConkey/New York Giants wide receiver
        Joe Collins/New York Yankees former player
        Dick McAuliffe/Detroit Tigers former player
        Rick Sutcliffe/Chicago Cubs
        Don Mattingly/New York Yankees
        Mark Gastineau/New York Jets
        Tom Landry/Dallas Cowboys coach
        Rance Mullinkis/Toronto Blue Jays
        Ken Anderson/Cincinnati Bengals
        Pat Ryan/New York Jets quarterback
        Glenn Hoffman/Boston Red Sox
        Billy Crystal/celebrity sport
        Mike Pagliarulo/New York Yankees
        George Martin/New York Giants defensive end
        Beasley Reece/Tampa Bay Buccaneers defensive back
        Chris McCarron/United States leading jockey
        Mike Quick/Philadelphia Eagles wide receiver
        Donnie Shell/Pittsburgh Steelers defensive back
        Peter Vidmar/United States Olympic gymnast champion
        Pat McInally/Cincinnati Bengals punters
      - Interviews, 1984 October 22-1985 February 19 (Offsite-box 4124, Item 75-86)
        Carl Lewis/1984 Olympic track champion
        Keith Fahnhorst/San Francisco 49ers offensive tackle
        Tom McMillen/Washington Bullets
        Ernie Banks/Hall of Famer
        Rosalyn Sumners/1984 Winter Olympics star
        Joe Theismann/Washington Redskins qaurterback
        Chuck Daly/Detroit Pistons coach
        Renaldo Nehemiah/San Francisco 49ers wide receiver
        Reggie Williams/Cincinnati Bengals linebacker
        Jim "Dusty" Rhodes/former New York Giants (baseball) player
        Peter Ueberroth/baseball commissioner
        Michael Jordan/Chicago Bulls
        Kelly Tripucka/Detroit Pistons
        Steve DeBerg/Tampa Bay Buccaneers quarterback
        Dan Bunz/San Francisco 49ers linebacker
        Nat Moore/Miami Dolphins wide receiver
        Joe Jacoby/Washington Redskins offensive tackle
        Cliff Robinson/Washington Bullets
        Terry Stieve/St. Louis Cardinals guard
        Sly Williams/Atlanta Hawks
        Joe Morris/New York Giants (football) running back
        Jim Jensen/Miami Dolphins
        Kevin Loughery/Chicago Bulls coach
        Trent Tucker/New York Knicks
        Dick "Night Train" Lane/NFL Hall of Famer
        Brad Benson/New York Giants tackle
        Art Still/Kansas City Chiefs defensive end
        Pat Tilley/St. Louis Cardinals wide receiver
        Herb Scott/Dallas Cowboys guard
        Rick Milot/Washington Redskins/linebacker
        Doug Flutie/1984 Heisman Trophy winner
        Richie Guerin/former NBA star and coach
        Gregg Buttle/New York Jets linebacker
        Lenny Moore/Baltimore Colts Hall of Famer
        Duffy Daugherty/former Michigan State football coach
        Julius Erving/Philadelphia 76ers
        Earl Campbell/New Orleans Saints
        Adrian Dantley/Utah Jazz
        Todd Blackledge/Kansas City Chiefs quarterback
        Lance Alworth/Pro Football Hall of Famer
        Vitas Gerulaitis/United States tennis pro
        Tom Gola/basketball Hall of Famer
        Rowdy Gaines/United States Olympic swimmer
        Jim Kovach/New Orleans Saints linebacker
        Clint Richardson/Philadelphia 76ers
        Dr. Roger Bannister/former international track star
        Aaron Krickstein/17 year-old United States tennis pro
        Steve Burtt/Golden State Warriors
        John Curry/world staking champion
        Gerry Coone/heavyweight contender
        Rusty Staub/New York Mets
        Danny Vranes/Seattle Supersonics
        Dennis Johnson/Boston Celtics
        Rafer Johnson/1960 Olympic decathlon champion
        Yoki Berra/New York Yankees manager
        Bill Fitch/Houston Rockets coach
        Phil Nierko/New York Yankees
        Bob Richards/former Olympic pole vault champion